Shajedul Arefin

Student | Tutor | Community Builder | Problem Solver

About Me

As a current student majoring in Computer Science and Engineering at BRAC University, I am an ambassador at MLSA(Microsoft Learn student Ambassadors). I offer three years of dedicated work in the community experience, with a strong focus on coding, mathematics, and AI . I am committed to leveraging my expertise to enhance peers' understanding and learning of new technologies.

Contact

+880 1768059361 shaiedul.arefin@g.bracu.ac.bd https://linkedin.com/in/shajedularefin/ https://github.com/mrbruce26

Skills

- Public Speaking
- Problem Solving
- Python
- Theme Paper Writing
- Excel
- Word
- PowerPoint

Language

Bengali, English, basic German

Certifications

- Basics of Robotics by ROBU
- German language certification

Experience

(2022 – 2023) JUNIOR EXECUTIVE - HR BURED - Brac University

(2023 – Present) BETA AMBASSADOR - MLSA Expertise: Computer Vision, Python, C, C++ MLSA - Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador

(2023 – Present) SENIOR EXECUTIVE - PR INSTRUCTOR - DATA STRUCTURE BUCC - Brac University Computer Club

(2022 – 2024) Apprentice - E&P ROBU - Robotics Club of Brac University

Education

(2022 – Present)
BRAC UNIVERSITY
Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering
Current CGPA: 3.55

(2019 – 2021) Dhaka Commerce College

AI related Projects

Predicting real time traffic and congestion hotspot in dhaka city

Employee attrition analysis